<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on piotrek-k.pl</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/</link><description>Recent content in Home on piotrek-k.pl</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2022 Piotr Kozerski</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:04:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://piotrek-k.pl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Distributed instant messaging protocol</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_communication/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 18:07:04 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_communication/</guid><description>A text messaging system that operates as a distributed network of devices. It is intended to allow communication between users without the need to run a central server. The system is able to continue working regardless of which network member is shut down. Based on idea of Distibuted Hash Table and Kademlia protocol.
Carried out in the form of an master&amp;rsquo;s thesis.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 17:03:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/about/</guid><description>Website built using Hugo static site generator, theme based on risotto</description></item><item><title>Topicly</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/topicly/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/topicly/</guid><description>An app for finding people to discuss. User could create his own topic and wait for other users to respond. Finding other peoples&amp;rsquo;s topics were done in a manner similar to how matching on Tinder works. University project - I was responsible for backend part (ASP.NET core).
Source code available here</description></item><item><title>Distributed directory</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_directory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_directory/</guid><description>Carried out in the form of an engineering thesis. Program that can exchange data between computers without central server in a way similar to BitTorrent.
The project has been divided into three parts:
Backbone - part responsible for establishing P2P network connections - fully published on Github and as NuGet package - more details here Distributed directory - part described in this post - not published online yet Mobile client - based on Xamarin - more details here Project described in details here (polish version only): praca_inzynierska.</description></item><item><title>Distributed directory for mobile</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_directory_xamarin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/distributed_directory_xamarin/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s basically Distributed directory project, with mobile-friendly UI on top of it. Thanks to C# being multiplatform, it was relatively easy to port it to Android devices by using Xamarin. Source code of this project is yet to be published.
Screenshot:</description></item><item><title>P2PNetworkBuilder</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/p2p_network_builder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:21:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/p2p_network_builder/</guid><description>P2PNetworkBuilder is a tool that provides a framework for creating networks of devices in Peer-to-peer manner. Is such networks, all devices are connected to each other. You can use it as a backbone of decentralized systems.
Key features:
Uses UDP Hole Punching technique to connect devices hidden behind NATs Provides end-to-end encryption of sent message&amp;rsquo;s content Uses public-key cryptography to exchange keys Operates on custom UDP based Internet protocol which ensures packet delivery in correct order Detects network memebers automatically.</description></item><item><title>Car tracking system</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/car_tracking_system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/car_tracking_system/</guid><description>Prototype of tracking system for vehicle sharing service. Designed as part of a university course related to IoT.
Using GPS and Arduino to gather location data Displaying gethered data on map in web-based control panel</description></item><item><title>C++ multithreading</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/cpp_multithreading/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/cpp_multithreading/</guid><description>Link to project</description></item><item><title>Open notes</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/open_notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/open_notes/</guid><description>Abandoned
Website for exchaning nodes, written in ASP.net. Heavily inspired by (now shut down) Stack Overflow Docs.</description></item><item><title>TaskManager</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/managing_tasks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/managing_tasks/</guid><description>Abandoned
University project, getting started with webdev using Angular.</description></item><item><title>MessengerDataOrganizer</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/messenger_data_organizer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/messenger_data_organizer/</guid><description>Abandoned
Link to project
At a time of creating this script, all messages exported from Facebook were placed in single html file and all pictures were placed in single directory. This made it difficult to view the data. This script extracts all metadata from there and saves it to database in order to let user run SQL scripts on it. It also organizes pictures into folders.
Data format provided by Facebook might change since then; compare it to this template to check if script is still usable.</description></item><item><title>Learning vocabulary / Nauka słówek</title><link>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/nsonline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://piotrek-k.pl/projects/nsonline/</guid><description>Abandoned (but still available)
Web app similar to Anki for learning vocabulary of foreign languages.
Available here (polish language only). Keep in mind it&amp;rsquo;s not actively developed since 2014.</description></item></channel></rss>